# 現在這個 場地裡的狗太多啦
There are too many, too many dogs in this site now.
# 抓兩條小狗 放到下面場地裡面去
Let me catch two puppies, and bring them down to the new site.
# 你看 這條 這個小母狗
Look! This one, is a little girl.
# 把你們兩兄妹
I'll take you with your brother.
# 看一條公的
Get me a boy.
# 你喜歡哪個
Who do you like?
# 你選一個
Choose one!
# 把你帶到下面去
I'll bring you down to the new site.
# 要誰
Who?
# 啊 快點 要誰
Ah! Be quick! Who do you want?
# 兩個都不喜歡 它喜歡袋子
She wants neither, but the bag.
# 就這條
Then this one
# 誒 喜歡你這條
Ey! This one likes you.
# 誒 你不去呀 捉下面這條去
Ey? You're not going? Let me catch the one down there.
# 你下不下
Are you going?
# 就這兩條
Alright! These two.
# 這最胖的
This is the fattest puppy,
# 最胖的
the fattest one.
# 你看 這個是最胖的這個
Look! This is the fattest puppy, you know.
# 哇瑟 下去
Oh god! Let's go,
# 下去
let's go,
# 下去玩啦 可以帶到他們
let's go and have fun there. Now I can take them away.
# 現在已經斷奶啦 可以吃飯啦
Now they've already weaned, and can have their own meals.
# 抱到那 把它帶到那個新的
Let's take them, bring them to the new,
# 新的廠房(註︰原字幕出錯，應該是「場地」)裡面去
to the new site.
# 誒 是一公一母
Ey! A boy and a girl.
# 這個 小黑 小黑 小黃狗
These little black, black, brown puppies.
# 看一下你們怎麼搞的
Let me see what happened to you two.
# 你看 它們兩個來到這裡怎麼這樣子啦
Look! What happened to these two puppies in this new site?
# 那麼激動
They're so excited!
# 這裡也是你的家
This is also your home.
# 好激動啊 它們
They're really excited,
# 一直跟著我
and are always following me.
# 不要我走
They're not letting me go.
# 上不來
You can't come up?
# 你看 這個 最胖的狗
Have a look at this, this fattest dog!
# 就你啦 就你最胖
Yea, it's you. You're the fattest.
# 你看著我幹嘛
Why are you looking at me?
# 說你胖 你
I said you are fat.
# 不能說嗎
Does it upset you?
# 一直看著我 以後你在這裡玩啦
It keeps looking at me. From now on this is your playground.
# 多大的場地 又沒人跟你搶吃的
It's an enormous site. And all food will be yours and only yours.
# 多好哇 在這裡
What a wonderful place!
# 別那麼激動 摸一下你這邊 那麼激動
Don't be too excited! I'm just petting you here. Don't be so excited.